ZARA KHAN

Front-end Web Developer

Lahore, Pakistan

+92 3126208985

ZaraMustafa@ymail.com

in /TheZaraKhan

Dedicated Web Designer with 4+ years of comprehensive experience in visual Design, Typography, Responsive and Mobile Websites & Custom CMS designs. With Excellent skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Adobe Graphic Suite I am a passionate designer with creative thinking and project design abilities and provides strong attention to detail and design quality.

SKILLS & EXPERTIES

Soft Skills:

- Time management
- Communication Skills
- Critical Thinking
- Decision making
- Creativity Team Work

Hard Skills:

- HTML5
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- WordPress
- Wireframing
- CSS3
- Tailwind CSS
- jQuery
- October CMSTypography
- wind CSS Sketch
 - Invision

Tools

- Microsoft Office
- GIT Atlassian

- Adobe Graphic Suite

- Figma,

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Dec 2018 – present

Web Developer and Designer at BlueLion Web Studio, Lahore, Pakistan

- ✓ Developed fully functional responsive prototypes based on Business Requirements using HTML/HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and jQuery.
- ✓ Developed unique user experiences that drove interaction, using JavaScript.
- ✓ Worked on new and existing micro-sites, landing pages, and templates to provide guidance and troubleshooting support to clients.
- ✓ Maintained client websites on an ongoing basis.

Nov 2017 – Nov 2018

Web Developer and Designer at United Vision, Lahore, Pakistan

- ✓ Communicating with clients about website updates
- ✓ Recreates website designs to improve the performance.
- ✓ Managing the client's ecommerce stores (updates and backups)
- ✓ Creating UX designs for client's ecommerce stores

Feb 2017 – Oct 2017

Frontend Web Developer at Xgeeksters, Lahore, Pakistan

- ✓ Front end Developer and UI Designer.
- ✓ Worked on AngularJS, Bootstrap, jQuery, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop

QUALIFICATION

2018 - 2020

MSCS - Masters in Computer Science

COMSATS University Islamabad, Pakistan

2013 - 2017

BSCS - Bachelors in Computer Science

Lahore College for Women University, Pakistan